An adventure of the senses.
Wild Orchid is a drama, romance film directed by Zalman King.
A woman lawyer becomes mesmerized by a self-made millionaire during an
encounter in Rio setting off a series of erotic encounters.
Emily Reed, played by Carré Otis.
James Wheeler, played by Mickey Rourke.
Claudia Dennis, played by Jacqueline Bisset.
Hanna Munch, played by Assumpta Serna.
Jerome McFarland, played by Bruce Greenwood.
Otto Munch, played by Oleg Vidov.
Wild Orchid is a 1989 American erotic romantic drama film directed by Zalman King and
starring Mickey Rourke, Jacqueline Bisset, Carré Otis, and Assumpta Serna.
A sequel, Wild Orchid II: Two Shades of Blue, was released in 1991.
The tone is emotional.